Hey everyone! Welcome to this video! It's a latex video and when you think of
latex brands you usually have European and Northern American brands in mind.
But today I'm going to show you a latex label from China which I think is really
high quality and innovative. I've done a video with them before, the Satin
Spandex Sentai video with Dream Mask. I will show you some pictures. And today I
I have this rubber bunny dream mask catsuit made of latex for you.
I'm really excited to try it on.
I first have to show you something though.
They put a little comic inside in which they explain the wearing and cleaning notes.
And you have the rubber bunny here.
I mean, how adorable is that?
The whole booklet is in this style and it's just so cute.
and there's a cute origin story really cute I just love this I mean it's a bunny wearing a
catsuit okay let's unpack this the catsuit was already
oiled up which is quite unusual but really really handy so I didn't have to clean and shine it up
Alright, this is the catsuit. It has some transparent parts and it's mostly black.
And I will get changed. And see you in a sec.
I managed to get into it. It's 0.4mm gorge and called Caramel Pearls.
I think because of the color scheme here we have going on we have transparent
black and black and yes I'm wearing a bra underneath because we here on
YouTube also the model in the webshop wears a bra underneath I think it's a
cool design feature if you don't want to be too revealing you can wear different
colored bras or different shaped bras to like spice it up a bit or just simply
pasties for example. The most prominent feature is the sleeve cut here. We have the puffy sleeves.
Like really really puffy. I kind of love it. To be honest I had to get used to puffy sleeves.
In the beginning I was opposed to them but by now I just think they look really cool.
because they change your type of figure a bit and now I have broad shoulders it catches the
light nicely all the different latex and reflections going on as I mentioned before
rubber bunny is a sub-brand of dream mask dream mask has several sub-brands I've shown you the
Sentai before for example. They have a lot of other sub brands with very specific products,
very specific masks and gender swap stuff and I could show you the pictures but I mean I have to
blur them obviously so you better check it out yourself. I will put the link in the description
text so go and have a look it's very interesting. Before I forget it let me turn around for a
so you can see the backside. Kind of love the nice cut here. I think it looks
really cool with the split body, the transparent black and the black. And I'm
wearing it open now. I could of course close this zipper. Now I'm gonna close it.
looks more dressed obviously and I think already a bit more dominant. I was
thinking about styling it up a bit because normally when I would go out
wearing this catsuit I would put things on top of it. Maybe gloves, maybe a
corset. Let's see and find out. Alright, of course if I'm going to add rubber it's
going to be more of a heavy rubber fetish look. These are chlorinated so they're super
fast to dress but they're also not as shiny. They don't hold the shine too much or long
enough but I just love that I can get into them so fast. And this is a corset bed. I
love this because it's super easy to dress with the zipper. Just going to put that on
of it. I feel with the corset the puffy sleeves are even more noticeable
anyway but they're more on display because the body is even slimmer and the puffy sleeves
are even wider optically. Okay I think there are some metal accessories missing
you know what's going to come.
I have a steel belt here.
It's a tiny one, this time.
It's self-made, by the way.
No, it's not lockable, as everyone keeps asking me.
Here we go.
And I do have matching bracelets.
Oh they're noisy.
And I think for this look I'm going to close the zipper again.
Yeah this is the fetish party look.
I know the word I've been looking for in my head all the time.
Regal.
I feel very regal with the puppy sleeves like a monarch or a queen.
And having the fluffy robes.
Ha!
Yeah, that's a cool look. It's a total
finish-prime look. I want to open it again because I just prefer it that way.
And it's a tiny bit more comfortable
to not have something
tight on the neck.
But I could also add a choker now again.
Anyway, these are really noisy.
Not using them that often.
I like it. I also like the transparent black in combination with the black and steel accessories and the bra underneath.
I think it's a cool look. I hope you'll like it too.
Thanks to Dream Mask and Rubber Bunny for sending this along. I really adore it.
Let me know in the comments what you think. Which look do you prefer?
The plain one from the beginning or the dressed up one like this?
and check out Dreamers homepage, I'll link everything down below.
I will see you in the next video and I wish you have a nice day. Bye!